这是为什么呢？
What’s going on here?
实际上有两种现象在起作用：
There are actually two phenomena at play:
痛苦的经历和被称作为 伤害感受的生物过程。
the experience of pain, and a biological  process called nociception.
伤害感受是神经系统中
Nociception is part of the nervous  system’s protective response
对有害或潜在有害刺激 保护性反应的一部分。
to harmful or potentially harmful stimuli.
传感器处于专门的神经末梢，
Sensors in specialized nerve endings
用于检测机械、热和化学威胁。
detect mechanical, thermal,  and chemical threats.
如果足够多的传感器被激活，
If enough sensors are activated,
电信号从神经输出到脊椎和大脑。
electrical signals shoot up the nerve  to the spine and on to the brain.
大脑衡量这些信号重要性，
The brain weighs the importance  of these signals